Elizabeth Boggs

Light Housekeeping - Open Systems Health Care Inc

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Elizabeth-Boggs/2dc26bd4fca31d72

A cashier at Pathmark for 3 years. Home Health Aid with 2 years of experience in healthcare. Skilled in providing care for people with disabilities. Providing meals, housekeeping, doing actives, washing clothes and anything else that needs to be done.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Light Housekeeping

Open Systems Health Care Inc - Bala-Cynwyd, PA - March 2013 to Present

Bala Cynwyd, PA 19004

Home Health Aid

March 2013 - Current

Delivered in-home care to disabled adults.

Ensured safety and well-being of patients.

Assisted patients with bathing, dressing, hygiene, and grooming.

Completed all daily living tasks to enhance the quality of life of elderly patients.

Helped residents with bathing, dressing, feeding, lifting and transferring.

Meal Preparation

Light Housekeeping

Assist With Medical Appointments

Cashier

Pathmark - Philadelphia, PA - September 2012 to 2015

Bagged groceries

Made sure the customers were happy

Kept a clean environment

EDUCATION

High School Diploma

Constitution HS - Philadelphia, PA 2011

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SKILLS

Healthy meal preparation Computer Skills Problem Solver Multitasker Team Player

Cashier